uspatriottactical.com 2019-12-17

# US Patriot Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how information about you is collected, used, and disclosed by U.S. Patriot, LLC and our subsidiaries (collectively, “US Patriot,” “we” or “us”) when you access or use our websites or mobile services (“Site”), shop in our stores, or otherwise interact with us.

## What We Collect

_Information you provide to us   _

We may collect personal data or personally identifiable information (collectively, “Personal Data”) from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.  Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and/or credit card information.  All of this information is considered “Personal Data.”  Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.  We will collect Personal Data personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.  Users can always refuse to supply Personal Data personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site- related activities. 

_Information collected automatically online_

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.  We also capture some information about your device, such as your IP address, and information related to your visit to our Site, such as the time-stamp, the page(s) or product(s) you viewed, and your log-in. 

## How we use collected information

_To personalize user experience_

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. We may also use your specific Personal Data to remember you when you log in again, so that you do not need to re-authenticate yourself, to let you browse between products and pages more easily, to remember if you put something in your shopping cart before you decide to checkout or leave the Site, and to administer content, promotions, surveys or other Site features.

_To improve our Site_

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from Users.

_To improve customer service_

User information helps us to respond more effectively to customer service requests and support needs.

_To process transactions_

We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

_To send periodic emails_

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

Personal Data will be stored by us for as long as you maintain an account with us or as needed to provide you services, resolve disputes, and comply with our legal obligations. 

We are based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law.  Your use or access to our site constitutes your consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.  

## How we protect your information

We use multiple information-security measures to protect your transactions with us.

We adopt reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of Personal Data under our control and appropriately limit access to it. 

Our Site uses SSL secured communication channel with digital signatures to encrypt and protect Personal Data exchanged between the Site and its Users.

## How we share your information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Personal Data to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personal Data regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We use an external provider to run our store, BigCommerce.  BigCommerce is based in the United States and is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and committed to providing best-in-class service and data protection.  You can check BigCommerce’s participation in the Privacy Shield on the official site of The International Trade Administration (ITA), U.S. Department of Commerce (www.privacyshield.gov).

## Advertising, Analytics and Services

We may allow third-party service providers to serve advertisements or provide analytical services.  Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on those sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. Those sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing on and interacting with any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. 

Ads appearing on our Site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Your Choices

Users may elect to stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, mobile marketing communications, phone or direct mail.  Users may also request that we delete their Personal Data, which may result in a User’s inability to continue to engage in certain Site-related activities.

Users may update and their correct your personal information at any time.   

## Changes to this Policy

U.S. Patriot, LLC has the discretion to update this policy at any time. When we do, we will  notify you by revising the Effective Date below, or in some cases we may provide an e-mail or  post a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage Users to check this page frequently for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the Personal Data we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this policy, or our privacy practices please contact us.

Phone: (800) 805-5294.  
Email: [admin@uspglobal.com](mailto:admin@uspglobal.com)  
Address:  
U.S. Patriot, LLC  
212 Candi Lane  
Columbia, SC 29210
